It's been a while.
久しぶりです
You look sleepy.
眠そうだね
Are you tired?
疲れてるの?
sleepy.
眠たい
What time did you sleep last night?
昨日何時寝たの?
2時?
Pickpocket?
すり?
It's not too late.
もう遅くないね
What time did you wake up?
何時に起きたの?
Lunch.
お昼
That was the kind of sleep you get when you sleep too much.
あれ、寝過ぎた時の眠りだったじゃん
vice versa.
逆に
I feel more refreshed if I live a relatively regular life.
割と規則正しく生きている方が スッキリする
surely.
確かに
I feel sleepier when I sleep during the day.
昼間寝たりする方が眠たい
I brought some alcohol.
酒持ったよ
terrible.
やばい
This is seriously dangerous.
マジでやばい
That's good.
良いね
I like women's clothes.
女性の服装、嬉しいよ
I thought it would be good when it got iced.
氷した時よっしゃと思って
It's warm today.
今日温かいもんね
yes.
そう
What's wrong with this?
どうしたのこれ?
I no longer wear them with boots.
ブーツで着なくなっちゃった
It's colored.
色付いてる
It's worn out.
使い古してるんだよ
I don't value things.
物大切にしてないな
He's a good boy.
良い子だよ
Is it an important present?
大事なプレゼントか
It's really dirty.
めっちゃ汚いよ
It was Uniqlo, so
ちょっとこれユニクロだったから、
Let's go buy some.
買いに行こう
Don't do it.
体しないで
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
feel ill?
気持ち悪い?
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
A flicker of light.
いちいちチラチラ
It's nothing.
なんでもないですよ
It's definitely hot today.
今日絶対暑いよ、それ
It was really hot.
めっちゃ暑かった
I thought I didn't need everyone.
みんないらんなと思って
I didn't even need a jacket.
上着もいらんかった
It's so hot.
めっちゃ暑い
This is all you need.
これだけでいけんね
Isn't it quite dangerous?
だいぶやばくない?
I have a somewhat unusual brush.
なんか珍しいブラシしてる
This is a dangerous pine.
やばいマツだ
I need to lose weight.
痩せないと
I'm saying this because summer has already started.
もう夏始まんで言ってる
Seriously dangerous?
マジでやばい?
terrible.
やばい
That knit thing is on it.
ニットのあれがついてる
Seriously?
マジ?
terrible.
やばい
Absolutely made.
絶対つくり
Anyone.
誰でも
It's been a long time since I came here.
久々に来たから
The sides are nice and deep.
いい感じに脇が深い
You might like it.
好きかもしれない
Her face is cute and her skin is beautiful.
顔かわいいし、肌きれいだね
Just socks are dirty, aren't they?
靴下だけって汚いよね
by chance.
たまたま
Let's go to sleep.
寝ようやろ
I just ate oysters, so I don't know anything about salty.
さっきガキ食べたから、 石指しょっぱいもの知らない
Did you turn your face?
顔向けたの?
Did you get sunburned?
日焼けした?
Maybe.
かもしれない
I can call you right away.
すぐ呼べる
Try a chest of drawers.
タンスをしてみて
Let's do leg splitting and drawing too.
足割りと絵もやろう
Stand back,
後ろ倒して、
On the soles of your feet,
足 裏にして、
Stretch out your front.
手 前を伸ばして
Azui?
あずい?
Are you being played with?
遊ばれてるの?
Are you going to serve something?
何か出すの?
Please take it out.
出してください
I hate it, seriously.
嫌だ、マジで
Please let it flow.
流してください
Thank you, you can run it.
ありがとう、流していいよ
thank you.
ありがとう